I wonder how many of you will read this article or listen to my voice right through to the end?
我想知道你们中有多少人会把这篇文章读完或者把我的语音完整地听到最后呢？
With our busy lifestyles and continuous distractions, it‘s hard to stay focussed on one task and I wouldn’t be surprised if I lose you somewhere along the way – but we‘ll see!
由于忙碌的生活方式和持续不断的干扰，我们很难专注于一项任务，如果在这个过程中我失去了你们的关注，我也不会感到惊讶——不过我们走着瞧吧！
Some experts believe that our attention spans are actually shrinking.
一些专家认为我们的注意力持续时间实际上正在缩短。
We often joke that goldfish have the shortest level of concentration, so much so that they forget what they saw nine seconds earlier.
我们常常开玩笑说金鱼的注意力集中时间最短，以至于它们会忘记九秒钟前看到的东西。
Well now a study says that humans have an even shorter span – just eight seconds.
现在一项研究表明，人类的注意力持续时间甚至更短——只有八秒钟。
This I can believe – there’s always so much to do and so much to remember that my brain gets overloaded and I find it hard to zero in on one thing.
这一点我能相信——总是有那么多事情要做，那么多事情要记住，我的大脑变得不堪重负，我发现很难专注于一件事情。
Of course, smartphones, the internet and social media all take up a lot of our attention.
当然，智能手机、互联网和社交媒体都占据了我们很多的注意力。
Chicago-based research firm Dscout found that we look at our mobile phones for, on average, 2.42 hours every day.
总部位于芝加哥的研究公司Dscout发现，我们平均每天看手机的时间为2.42小时。
It is tempting to keep glancing at our phones when we should be focussing on other things and it‘s something we didn’t and couldn‘t do before the boom in digital media and smartphones, so maybe that’s why the amount of time we can concentrate has been dropping.
我们应该专注于其他事情的时候，总是忍不住想扫一眼手机，而在数字媒体和智能手机蓬勃发展之前，我们不会也不能这样做，所以也许这就是为什么我们能够集中注意力的时间一直在减少。
A report carried out for Microsoft said the average human attention span in 2000 was 12 seconds but has now fallen to just eight seconds.
为微软公司进行的一项报告称，2000年人类的平均注意力持续时间为12秒，但现在已经下降到只有8秒了。
However, a BBC radio programme called More or Less, couldn‘t find evidence to back up Microsoft’s report.
然而，英国广播公司一档名为《或多或少》的广播节目未能找到支持微软报告的证据。
It spoke to Dr Gemma Briggs, a psychologist at the Open University, who says there are problems with the idea of measuring attention spans and it‘s all down to the individual person, “so attention-switching ability may well have developed in recent years, in the age of the smartphone and the internet.
该节目采访了开放大学的心理学家杰玛·布里格斯博士，她说衡量注意力持续时间的这个概念存在问题，而且这完全取决于个人，“所以在智能手机和互联网时代，注意力切换能力很可能在近年来得到了发展。
But because someone’s distracted by their smartphone... it doesn‘t mean that they then don’t have the ability to control and sustain their attention when they carry out another task.”
但是，仅仅因为有人被他们的智能手机分散了注意力......并不意味着当他们执行另一项任务时，就没有能力控制和保持他们的注意力。”
This suggests we‘re getting better at switching our attention quickly between different tasks; we can multi-skill better than before so we can achieve more things.
这表明我们在不同任务之间快速切换注意力的能力正在提高；我们比以前更能具备多种技能，所以我们可以完成更多的事情。
This is useful in the modern workplace where we need to turn our hand to many different jobs.
这在现代职场中很有用，因为在职场中我们需要从事许多不同的工作。
But for people who want to grab our attention, such as advertisers, they have to think of clever ways to make us sit up and take notice of them.
但是对于那些想要吸引我们注意力的人，比如广告商，他们必须想出巧妙的方法让我们感兴趣并注意到他们。
And there are still times when something demands our full attention, without any distractions, like reading or listening to this article.
而且仍然有一些时候，有些事情需要我们全神贯注，不被任何事情干扰，比如阅读或者听这篇文章。
Did you make it to the end?!
你坚持看到（听到）最后了吗？！